Archival Collective Bargaining Agreements File 6030
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- State, County '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 172, Folder 12)
- State County '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 172, Folder 13)
- State, County 1955-1963 (Box 172, Folder 14)
- State, County '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 172, Folder 15)
- State, County '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 172, Folder 16)
- State, County and Municipal Agreements, 1960-1964 (Box 172, Folder 17)
- State, County and Municipal Workers, 1970-1989 (Box 173, Folder 1)
- State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1967-1968 (Box 173, Folder 2)
- State, County and Municipal Employees, 1961-1966 (Box 173, Folder 3)
- State, County, Municipal Workers 1965-1969 (Box 173, Folder 4)
- State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1971-1982 (Box 173, Folder 5)
- State County and Municipal Employees, 1971-1979 (Box 173, Folder 6)
- State County and Municipal Employees, 1977 (Box 173, Folder 7)
- State, County, Municipal Employees 1970- (Box 173, Folder 8)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 1978-1979 (Box 173, Folder 9)
- Steelworkers International Employees Independent Union 1971 (Box 173, Folder 10)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1945-1947 (Box 174, Folder 1)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1945-1949 (Box 174, Folder 2)
- Steelworkers of America, United, 1937-1946 (Box 174, Folder 3)
- Steelworkers 1947 (Box 174, Folder 4)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1945-1949 (Box 174, Folder 5)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1945 (Box 174, Folder 6)
- Steelworkers, 1949-1950 (Box 175, Folder 1)
- Steelworkers, 1949-1951 (Box 175, Folder 2)
- Steelworkers 1952 (Box 175, Folder 3)
- Steelworkers 1950-51, 1950-1951 (Box 175, Folder 4)
- Steelworkers, 1949 (Box 175, Folder 5)
- Steelworkers, 1947-1952 (Box 175, Folder 6)
- Steelworkers, 1949-1951 (Box 175, Folder 7)
- Steelworkers, United, 1949-1951 (Box 175, Folder 8)
- United Steelworkers, 1952 (Box 176, Folder 1)
- United Steelworkers, 1952 (Box 176, Folder 2)
- Steelworkers, United, 1952-1954 (Box 176, Folder 3)
- Steelworkers, United, 1952-1954 (Box 176, Folder 4)
- Steelworkers, United, 1952-1954 (Box 176, Folder 5)
- Steelworkers, United '53-'54, 1953-1954 (Box 176, Folder 6)
- Steelworkers, United, 1952-1954 (Box 176, Folder 7)
- United Steelworkers, 1955-1960 (Box 177, Folder 1)
- United Steelworkers, 1955-1961 (Box 177, Folder 2)
- United Steelworkers, 1955-1960 (Box 177, Folder 3)
- United Steelworkers, 1956-1961 (Box 177, Folder 4)
- Steelworkers 1955-1959 (Box 177, Folder 5)
- Steelworkers 1955-1959 (Box 177, Folder 6)
- Steelworkers, 1955-1959 (Box 177, Folder 7)
- Steelworkers, United, 1955-1960 (Box 178, Folder 1)
- Steelworkers, United, 1955-1960 (Box 178, Folder 2)
- United Steelworkers, 1956-1959 (Box 178, Folder 3)
- United Steelworkers, 1956-1959 (Box 178, Folder 4)
- Steelworkers of America, United, 1957-1958 (Box 178, Folder 5)
- United Steelworkers, 1955-1959 (Box 178, Folder 6)
- United Steelworkers, 1956-1959 (Box 178, Folder 7)
- United Steelworkers, 1960-1965 (Box 179, Folder 1)
- United Steelworkers, 1960-1965 (Box 179, Folder 2)
- United Steelworkers, 1960-1965 (Box 179, Folder 3)
- United Steelworkers, 1960-1965 (Box 179, Folder 4)
- United Steelworkers, 1960-1965 (Box 179, Folder 5)
- United Steelworkers, 1960-1965 (Box 179, Folder 6)
- United Steelworkers, 1960-1965 (Box 179, Folder 7)
- United Steelworkers, 1960-1964 (Box 179, Folder 8)
- Steelworkers 1960-1964 (Box 179, Folder 9)
- United Steelworkers, 1960-1965 (Box 180, Folder 1)
- United Steelworkers, 1960-1964 (Box 180, Folder 2)
- Steelworkers of America, 1960-1965 (Box 180, Folder 3)
- United Steelworkers, 1960-1965 (Box 180, Folder 4)
- United Steelworkers, 1960-1965 (Box 180, Folder 5)
- United Steelworkers, 1960-1965 (Box 180, Folder 6)
- United Steelworkers, 1960-1965 (Box 180, Folder 7)
- United Steelworkers, 1963 (Box 180, Folder 8)
- Steelworkers of America, United '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 180, Folder 9)
- United Steelworkers, 1965-1969 (Box 181, Folder 1)
- United Steelworkers, 1965-1969 (Box 181, Folder 2)
- United Steelworkers, 1965-1969 (Box 181, Folder 3)
- United Steelworkers, 1968-1970 (Box 181, Folder 4)
- United Steelworkers, 1965-1970 (Box 181, Folder 5)
- United Steelworkers, 1965-1970 (Box 181, Folder 6)
- Steelworkers 1965-1969 (Box 181, Folder 7)
- United Steelworkers, 1965-1969 (Box 181, Folder 8)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1970-1974 (Box 182, Folder 1)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1971-1974 (Box 182, Folder 2)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1970-1974 (Box 182, Folder 3)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1970-1974 (Box 182, Folder 4)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1970-1974 (Box 182, Folder 5)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1970-1974 (Box 182, Folder 6)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1970-1974 (Box 182, Folder 7)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1970-1974 (Box 182, Folder 8)
- United Steelworkers, 1960-1965 (Box 183, Folder 1)
- United Steelworkers, 1969-1975 (Box 183, Folder 2)
- United Steelworkers, 1990-1993 (Box 183, Folder 3)
- United Steelworkers, 1980-1983 (Box 183, Folder 4)
- Steelworkers 1980- (Box 183, Folder 5)
- Steelworkers 1975-79, 1975-1979 (Box 183, Folder 6)
- Steelworkers Organizing Committee, 1948-1960 (Box 183, Folder 7)
- Steelworkers Workers, Union, 1964-1965 (Box 183, Folder 8)
- Stereotypers 1915-1928 (Box 183, Folder 9)
- Stereotypers 1922-1944 (Box 183, Folder 10)
- Stereotypers' '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 183, Folder 11)
- Stereotyper's '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 183, Folder 12)
- Stereotypers and Electrotypers Un. Of N. A. Agreements '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 183, Folder 13)
- Stereotypers, 1960-1964 (Box 184, Folder 1)
- Stereotypers' and Electrotypers' Union of N.A., International '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 184, Folder 2)
- Stereotypers 1960-1964 (Box 184, Folder 3)
- Stereotypers 1965-1968 (Box 184, Folder 4)
- Stereotypers 1969- (Box 184, Folder 5)
- Stone and Allied Products Workers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 184, Folder 6)
- Stone and Allied Products Workers '55-'60, 1955-1960 (Box 184, Folder 7)
- Stone Cutters, Journeyman 1919 (Box 184, Folder 8)
- Stove Mounters, 1954-1959 (Box 184, Folder 9)
- Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Emps, Agreements 1929-1944 (Box 184, Folder 10)
- Street, Electric Railway, 1943-1949 (Box 184, Folder 11)
- Street, Electric Railway, 1945-1949 (Box 184, Folder 12)
- Street, Electric Railway '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 184, Folder 13)
- Street, Electric Railway '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 184, Folder 14)
- Street, Electric Railway, 1955-1959 (Box 185, Folder 1)
- Street, Electric Railway, 1955-1959 (Box 185, Folder 2)
- Street, Electric Railway, 1955-1959 (Box 185, Folder 3)
- Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Ems. Agreements '55-'59 Amal. Assn., 1955-1959 (Box 185, Folder 4)
- Street, Electric Railway, 1962 (Box 185, Folder 5)
- Street, Electric Railway '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 185, Folder 6)
- Sugar Refinery Workers, United, United 1939-1944 (Box 185, Folder 7)
- Sugar Workers Council 1948 (Box 185, Folder 8)
- Taxi Drivers Union, NYC 1967 (Box 185, Folder 9)
- Teachers, American Federation of, 1962-1965 (Box 185, Folder 10)
- Teachers Association Vigo County Agreement, 1966 (Box 185, Folder 11)
- Teachers Ass'n., Ithaca, 1978 (Box 185, Folder 12)
- Teachers, New York State United (NYSUT) Agreements A-C, 1985-1991 (Box 185, Folder 13)
- Teachers, United Federation of, 1967-1982 (Box 185, Folder 14)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1958-1960 (Box 186, Folder 1)
- Brhd. Of Teamsters, 1956-1960 (Box 186, Folder 2)
- Brhd. Of Teamsters, 1958-1960 (Box 186, Folder 3)
- Teamsters,etc., 1958-1960 (Box 186, Folder 4)
- Teamster,etc., 1955-1965 (Box 186, Folder 5)
- Teamsters,etc., 1958-1961 (Box 186, Folder 6)
- Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1956-1959 (Box 186, Folder 7)
- Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers; International Brotherhood of - Agreements 1940-1944 (Box 186, Folder 8)
- Teamsters, etc., 1957-1961 (Box 186, Folder 9)
- Teamsters, etc., 1957-1959 (Box 186, Folder 10)
- Teamsters, etc., 1954-1956 (Box 186, Folder 11)
- Teamsters, etc., 1955-1960 (Box 186, Folder 12)
- Local 875 M-R, 1963-1965 (Box 187, Folder 1)
- Local 875 S-Z, 1960-1965 (Box 187, Folder 2)
- Local 818 A-D, 1959-1961 (Box 187, Folder 3)
- Local 824, 1959-1962 (Box 187, Folder 4)
- Local 812 A-M, 1955-1964 (Box 187, Folder 5)
- Local 813, 1961-1964 (Box 187, Folder 6)
- Local 812, 1962-1963 (Box 187, Folder 7)
- Local 816, 1960-1964 (Box 187, Folder 8)
- Local 875, 1958-1961 (Box 187, Folder 9)
- Local 814, 1959-1961 (Box 187, Folder 10)
- Local 820, 1956-1965 (Box 188, Folder 1)
- Local 819, 1959-1961 (Box 188, Folder 2)
- Local 852 (M-Z), 1959-1965 (Box 188, Folder 3)
- Local 852, 1954-1965 (Box 188, Folder 4)
- Local 818 E-Z, 1960-1963 (Box 188, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous, 1950-1969 (Box 188, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous, 1950-1969 (Box 188, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous, 1956-1960 (Box 188, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous, 1959-1960 (Box 188, Folder 9)
- Local 1034 A-Z, 1963-1965 (Box 189, Folder 1)
- Local 449, 1959-1967 (Box 189, Folder 2)
- Local 445, 1959-1965 (Box 189, Folder 3)
- Local 445 Part 2, 1959-1965 (Box 189, Folder 4)
- Local 852 A-F, 1962-1967 (Box 189, Folder 5)
- Local 852 N-Z, 1961-1966 (Box 189, Folder 6)
- Local 868 M-Z, 1960-1968 (Box 189, Folder 7)
- Local 917 A-Z, 1960-1969 (Box 189, Folder 8)
- Local 1205 A-Z, 1960-1969 (Box 189, Folder 9)
- Local 933, 1965-1967 (Box 189, Folder 10)
- Local 810, 1963-1967 (Box 190, Folder 1)
- Local 787, 1964-1967 (Box 190, Folder 2)
- Local 757, 1964-1967 (Box 190, Folder 3)
- Local 693, 1964-1966 (Box 190, Folder 4)
- Local 687 A-C, 1960-1967 (Box 190, Folder 5)
- Local 687 D-L, 1965-1967 (Box 190, Folder 6)
- Local 687 M-Z, 1965-1967 (Box 190, Folder 7)
- Local 584, 1965-1967 (Box 190, Folder 8)
- Local 607, 1963-1967 (Box 190, Folder 9)
- Local 649, 1964-1968 (Box 190, Folder 10)
- Local 648, 1964-1966 (Box 190, Folder 11)
- Local 602, 1964-1967 (Box 190, Folder 12)
- Local 669 A-K, 1965-1967 (Box 190, Folder 13)
- Local 669 L-Z, 1964-1967 (Box 190, Folder 14)
- Local 558 L, 1967-1968 (Box 190, Folder 15)
- Local 558 U-Z, 1964-1967 (Box 190, Folder 16)
- Local 558 S, 1960-1964 (Box 190, Folder 17)
- Local 558 T, 1965-1968 (Box 190, Folder 18)
- Local 645, 1964-1966 (Box 190, Folder 19)
- Local 529 A-C, 1965-1968 (Box 190, Folder 20)
- Local 456, 1965-1968 (Box 190, Folder 21)
- Agreements, 1955-1958 (Box 191, Folder 1)
- Agreements (Teamsters), 1957-1959 (Box 191, Folder 2)
- Teamsters, 1957-1959 (Box 191, Folder 3)
- Teamsters, 1955-1959 (Box 191, Folder 4)
- Teamsters, 1957-1959 (Box 191, Folder 5)
- Teamsters, 1955-1959 (Box 191, Folder 6)
- Teamsters, 1955-1959 (Box 191, Folder 7)
- Teamsters '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 191, Folder 8)
- Teamsters, 1955-1964 (Box 192, Folder 1)
- Agreements, 1960 (Box 192, Folder 2)
- Local 810 A, 1964-1968 (Box 192, Folder 3)
- Teamsters, 1962-1964 (Box 192, Folder 4)
- Teamsters, 1962-1964 (Box 192, Folder 5)
- Teamsters, 1964-1968 (Box 192, Folder 6)
- Teamsters, 1960-1964 (Box 192, Folder 7)
- Teamsters, 1960-1971 (Box 192, Folder 8)
- Teamsters, 1962-1966 (Box 192, Folder 9)
- Teamsters, 1963-1968 (Box 192, Folder 10)
- Teamsters, 1966-1971 (Box 192, Folder 11)
- Local 875 B-C, 1964-1968 (Box 193, Folder 1)
- Local 875 T-Z, 1964-1968 (Box 193, Folder 2)
- Local 875, 1952-1954 (Box 193, Folder 3)
- Agreements, 1964-1968 (Box 193, Folder 4)
- Agreements, 1964-1968 (Box 193, Folder 5)
- Agreements, 1962-1968 (Box 193, Folder 6)
- Agreements, 1962-1967 (Box 193, Folder 7)
- Agreements, 1962-1968 (Box 193, Folder 8)
- Teamsters, 1964-1968 (Box 195, Folder 1)
- Typographical World Journal Tribune 204-2346, 1967 (Box 195, Folder 2)
- Teamsters, Ind. The Krug Baking Co. of N.Y. Inc. 531-2086, 1959-1961 (Box 195, Folder 3)
- Toy Workers Welbilt Stove Co. Inc., 1962-1965 (Box 195, Folder 4)
- Newspaper Guild, 1963-1967 (Box 195, Folder 5)
- Local 445 A-H, 1963-1968 (Box 195, Folder 6)
- Local 449 Q-Z, 1963-1968 (Box 195, Folder 7)
- Local 449 M-P, 1969-1985 (Box 195, Folder 8)
- Local 449 D-L, 1964-1968 (Box 195, Folder 9)
- Local 449 A-C, 1964-1968 (Box 195, Folder 10)
- Local 445 Q-Z, 1964-1968 (Box 195, Folder 11)
- Local 445 I-P, 1964-1968 (Box 195, Folder 12)
- Local 182, 1962 (Box 196, Folder 1)
- Local 294, 1962 (Box 196, Folder 2)
- Local 295, 1960-1962 (Box 196, Folder 3)
- Local 300, 1960-1962 (Box 196, Folder 4)
- Local 202, 1963-1965 (Box 196, Folder 5)
- Local 167, 1967 (Box 196, Folder 6)
- Local 138, 1964-1967 (Box 196, Folder 7)
- Local 182, 1959-1962 (Box 196, Folder 8)
- Local 182, 1961-1965 (Box 196, Folder 9)
- Agreements, 1960-1962 (Box 197, Folder 1)
- Agreements, 1963-1965 (Box 197, Folder 2)
- Agreements - Teamsters, 1962-1964 (Box 197, Folder 3)
- Agreements - Teamsters, 1954-1955 (Box 197, Folder 4)
- Agreements - Teamsters, 1953-1956 (Box 197, Folder 5)
- Agreements - Teamsters, 1953-1956 (Box 197, Folder 6)
- Teamsters, 1954-1970 (Box 197, Folder 7)
- Agreements - Teamsters, 1967-1970 (Box 197, Folder 8)
- Agreements - Teamsters, 1960-1967 (Box 197, Folder 9)
- Teamsters, 1958-1959 (Box 198, Folder 1)
- Teamsters, 1960-1962 (Box 198, Folder 2)
- Teamsters, 1958-1965 (Box 198, Folder 3)
- Teamsters, 1960-1964 (Box 198, Folder 4)
- Teamsters, 1965-1967 (Box 198, Folder 5)
- Teamsters, 1961-1970 (Box 198, Folder 6)
- Teamsters, 1961-1967 (Box 198, Folder 7)
- Local 868, 1963-1967 (Box 199, Folder 1)
- Local 868 A-E, 1959-1965 (Box 199, Folder 2)
- Local 875, 1963-1965 (Box 199, Folder 3)
- Local 649, 1962-1965 (Box 199, Folder 4)
- Local 658, 1963-1965 (Box 199, Folder 5)
- Local 648, 1960-1966 (Box 199, Folder 6)
- Local 645, 1962-1965 (Box 199, Folder 7)
- Local 643, 1962-1963 (Box 199, Folder 8)
- Local 641, 1962-1964 (Box 199, Folder 9)
- Local 687, 1959-1962 (Box 199, Folder 10)
- Local 456, 1960-1961 (Box 199, Folder 11)
- Local 550, 1960 (Box 199, Folder 12)
- Local 476, 1960-1962 (Box 199, Folder 13)
- Local 529, 1960-1962 (Box 199, Folder 14)
- Local 540, 1960 (Box 199, Folder 15)
- Local 506, 1964 (Box 199, Folder 16)
- Local 118 R-Z, 1962-1965 (Box 200, Folder 1)
- Agreements, 1962-1965 (Box 200, Folder 2)
- Local 293, 1955-1956 (Box 200, Folder 3)
- Local 306, 1962-1965 (Box 200, Folder 4)
- Local 182, 1955-1965 (Box 200, Folder 5)
- Local 338, 1960 (Box 200, Folder 6)
- Local 282, 1955-1959 (Box 200, Folder 7)
- Local 327, 1953-1957 (Box 200, Folder 8)
- Local 272, 1957-1959 (Box 200, Folder 9)
- Local 277, 1959-1960 (Box 200, Folder 10)
- Local 317, 1958-1960 (Box 200, Folder 11)
- Local 264, 1954-1957 (Box 200, Folder 12)
- Local 316, 1952-1953 (Box 200, Folder 13)
- Local 816, 1955-1958 (Box 200, Folder 14)
- Local 817, 1956-1959 (Box 200, Folder 15)
- Local 813, 1960-1965 (Box 200, Folder 16)
- Local 812, 1955-1965 (Box 201, Folder 1)
- Local 804, 1954-1957 (Box 201, Folder 2)
- Local 757, 787, 794, 1958-1959 (Box 201, Folder 3)
- Local 719, 1957-1959 (Box 201, Folder 4)
- Local 707, 1958-1960 (Box 201, Folder 5)
- Local 693, 1958-1960 (Box 201, Folder 6)
- Local 802, 1952-1960 (Box 201, Folder 7)
- Local 687, 1954-1957 (Box 202, Folder 1)
- Local 669, 1956-1959 (Box 202, Folder 2)
- Local 649, 1956-1959 (Box 202, Folder 3)
- Local 648, 1955-1957 (Box 202, Folder 4)
- Local 854, 1955-1959 (Box 202, Folder 5)
- Local 852 A-G, 1957-1960 (Box 202, Folder 6)
- Local 852 R-Z, 1955-1959 (Box 202, Folder 7)
- Local 852 H-Q, 1955-1959 (Box 202, Folder 8)
- Local 819, 1955-1959 (Box 202, Folder 9)
- Local 449, 1961-1965 (Box 203, Folder 1)
- Local 398, 1961-1963 (Box 203, Folder 2)
- Local 398, 1961-1963 (Box 203, Folder 3)
- Local 398 L-Z, 1959-1963 (Box 203, Folder 4)
- Local 449 E-M, 1959-1962 (Box 203, Folder 5)
- Local 449 N-Z, 1955-1959 (Box 203, Folder 6)
- Local 812, 1965-1968 (Box 204, Folder 1)
- Local 812 I-N, 1965-1968 (Box 204, Folder 2)
- Local 812 A-B, 1965-1968 (Box 204, Folder 3)
- Local 812 H, 1963-1966 (Box 204, Folder 4)
- Local 812 C-G, 1963-1966 (Box 204, Folder 5)
- Local 719, 1961 (Box 204, Folder 6)
- Local 558, 1958-1965 (Box 204, Folder 7)
- Local 558, 1958-1965 (Box 204, Folder 8)
- Local 558, 1959-1965 (Box 204, Folder 9)
- Local 693, 1958-1962 (Box 204, Folder 10)
- Local 707, 1960-1963 (Box 204, Folder 11)
- Local 669, 1959-1965 (Box 204, Folder 12)
- Local 553, 1959-1965 (Box 204, Folder 13)
- Local 607, 1963-1965 (Box 204, Folder 14)
- Local 602, 1960-1964 (Box 204, Folder 15)
- Local 602, 1961-1964 (Box 204, Folder 16)
- Local 584, 1958-1964 (Box 204, Folder 17)
- Local 804 A-J, 1960-1965 (Box 205, Folder 1)
- Local 804 K-Z, 1957-1964 (Box 205, Folder 2)
- Local 791, 1960-1961 (Box 205, Folder 3)
- Local 787 N-Z, 1960-1965 (Box 205, Folder 4)
- Local 787 A-M, 1961-1964 (Box 205, Folder 5)
- Local 757, 1961-1965 (Box 205, Folder 6)
- Local 802, 1961-1965 (Box 205, Folder 7)
- Local 794, 1961-1964 (Box 205, Folder 8)
- Local 807, 1956-1965 (Box 205, Folder 9)
- Local 810, 1961-1965 (Box 205, Folder 10)
- Local 810 A-F, 1961-1965 (Box 205, Folder 11)
- Local 806, 1963-1965 (Box 205, Folder 12)
- Local 805, 1956-1957 (Box 205, Folder 13)
- Local 375, 1956-1958 (Box 206, Folder 1)
- Local 398, 1956-1959 (Box 206, Folder 2)
- Local 118 - A-G, 1956-1958 (Box 206, Folder 3)
- Local 118 H-Q, 1957-1959 (Box 206, Folder 4)
- Local 300, 1956-1958 (Box 206, Folder 5)
- Local 99, 1959-1960 (Box 206, Folder 6)
- Local 96, 1960-1965 (Box 206, Folder 7)
- Local 295, 1956-1960 (Box 206, Folder 8)
- Local 294, 1958 (Box 206, Folder 9)
- Local 146, 1956-1965 (Box 206, Folder 10)
- Local 240, 1960-1965 (Box 206, Folder 11)
- local 239, 1956-1959 (Box 206, Folder 12)
- Local 237, 1953-1954 (Box 206, Folder 13)
- Local 232, 1959-1960 (Box 206, Folder 14)
- Local 398 S--Z, 1961-1962 (Box 207, Folder 1)
- Local 476 (Box 207, Folder 2)
- Local 550, 1960-1965 (Box 207, Folder 3)
- Local 529 D-Z, 1960-1965 (Box 207, Folder 4)
- Local 558 C, 1964 (Box 207, Folder 5)
- Local 558 D-E, 1955-1967 (Box 207, Folder 6)
- Local 553, 1955-1967 (Box 207, Folder 7)
- Local 558 M-N, 1965-1968 (Box 207, Folder 8)
- Local 558 O-R, 1958-1960 (Box 207, Folder 9)
- Local 375 G-Z, 1961-1965 (Box 207, Folder 10)
- Local 558 A-B, 1965-1968 (Box 207, Folder 11)
- Local 558 F, 1960-1965 (Box 207, Folder 12)
- Local 558 G-K (Box 207, Folder 13)
- Local 398 D-H (Box 207, Folder 14)
- Local 398 A-C, 1960-1968 (Box 207, Folder 15)
- Local 294 H-J, 1965-1967 (Box 207, Folder 16)
- Local 294 S, 1964-1967 (Box 207, Folder 17)
- Local 382, 1968 (Box 207, Folder 18)
- Local 375 A-F, 1964-1967 (Box 207, Folder 19)
- Local 294 G, 1964-1967 (Box 207, Folder 20)
- Local 294 D-F, 1967 (Box 207, Folder 21)
- Local 294 M-N, 1965-1968 (Box 207, Folder 22)
- Teamsters, 1963-1967 (Box 208, Folder 1)
- Teamsters, 1957-1964 (Box 208, Folder 2)
- Teamsters, 1960-1964 (Box 208, Folder 3)
- Teamsters, 1960-1965 (Box 208, Folder 4)
- Teamsters, 1964-1967 (Box 208, Folder 5)
- Teamsters, 1964-1965 (Box 208, Folder 6)
- Teamsters, 1960-1965 (Box 208, Folder 7)
- Teamsters, 1963-1967 (Box 208, Folder 8)
- Teamsters, 1963-1967 (Box 208, Folder 9)
- Local 810 E-G, 1963-1966 (Box 209, Folder 1)
- Local 794, 1968 (Box 209, Folder 2)
- Local 810 B-D, 1961-1964 (Box 209, Folder 3)
- Local 813, 1965-1968 (Box 209, Folder 4)
- Local 812 S-Z, 1963-1967 (Box 209, Folder 5)
- Local 814, 1968-1970 (Box 209, Folder 6)
- Teamsters, 1960-1962 (Box 209, Folder 7)
- Teamsters, 1960-1962 (Box 209, Folder 8)
- Agreements, 1960-1964 (Box 209, Folder 9)
- T, 1960-1962 (Box 209, Folder 10)
- T, 1960-1962 (Box 209, Folder 11)
- Local 1015 A-Z, 1960-1964 (Box 210, Folder 1)
- Local 1030 A-Z, 1960-1966 (Box 210, Folder 2)
- Local 875 D-G, 1960-1965 (Box 210, Folder 3)
- Local 875 H-J, 1965-1968 (Box 210, Folder 4)
- Local 875 M, 1960-1965 (Box 210, Folder 5)
- Local 875 K-L, 1964-1966 (Box 210, Folder 6)
- Local 875 N-O, 1964-1967 (Box 210, Folder 7)
- Local 875 P-R, 1967-1968 (Box 210, Folder 8)
- Local 875 S, 1964-1967 (Box 210, Folder 9)
- Local 852 C-M, 1964-1966 (Box 210, Folder 10)
- Local 854, 1964-1966 (Box 210, Folder 11)
- Local 875 A, 1966-1968 (Box 210, Folder 12)
- Local 868 A-Z, 1965-1968 (Box 210, Folder 13)
- Local 802, 1963-1966 (Box 211, Folder 1)
- Local 791, 1968 (Box 211, Folder 2)
- Local 810 MB-R, 1964-1968 (Box 211, Folder 3)
- Local 810 S-Z, 1964-1967 (Box 211, Folder 4)
- Local 807, 1964-1968 (Box 211, Folder 5)
- Local 804 L-Z, 1962-1964 (Box 211, Folder 6)
- Local 806, 1964-1968 (Box 211, Folder 7)
- Local 824, 1963-1968 (Box 211, Folder 8)
- Local 804 A-L, 1965-1967 (Box 211, Folder 9)
- Local 818 K-Z, 1965-1968 (Box 211, Folder 10)
- Local 820, 1965-1968 (Box 211, Folder 11)
- Local 819, 1965-1968 (Box 211, Folder 12)
- Local 816, 1964-1968 (Box 211, Folder 13)
- Local 818 A-J, 1965-1968 (Box 211, Folder 14)
- Local 808, 1966-1968 (Box 211, Folder 15)
- Local 917, 1954-1960 (Box 212, Folder 1)
- Local 868, 875, 895, 1956-1960 (Box 212, Folder 2)
- Teamsters, 1960-1963 (Box 212, Folder 3)
- Teamsters, 1957-1964 (Box 212, Folder 4)
- Teamsters, 1956-1960 (Box 212, Folder 5)
- Teamsters, 1956-1960 (Box 212, Folder 6)
- Teamsters, 1956-1960 (Box 212, Folder 7)
- Teamsters, 1960-1964 (Box 212, Folder 8)
- Local 239, 1961-1963 (Box 213, Folder 1)
- Local 237, 1961-1964 (Box 213, Folder 2)
- Local 232, 1961-1965 (Box 213, Folder 3)
- Local 240, 1960-1964 (Box 213, Folder 4)
- Local 294, 1962-1964 (Box 213, Folder 5)
- Local 375, 1960-1962 (Box 213, Folder 6)
- Local 375, 1959-1963 (Box 213, Folder 7)
- Local 282, 1960-1964 (Box 213, Folder 8)
- Local 277, 1962-1965 (Box 213, Folder 9)
- Local 272, 1957-1965 (Box 213, Folder 10)
- Local 264, 1958-1961 (Box 213, Folder 11)
- Local 263, 1962-1964 (Box 213, Folder 12)
- Local 294, 1960-1963 (Box 213, Folder 13)
- Local 118 R-Z, 1961-1964 (Box 214, Folder 1)
- Local 118 M-Q, 1958-1964 (Box 214, Folder 2)
- Local 118 D-L, 1961-1964 (Box 214, Folder 3)
- Local 99, 1960-1963 (Box 214, Folder 4)
- Local 65, 1959-1963 (Box 214, Folder 5)
- Local 3, 1958-1962 (Box 214, Folder 6)
- Local 27, 1960-1962 (Box 214, Folder 7)
- Local 118 A-C, 1959-1962 (Box 214, Folder 8)
- Local 316, 1960-1962 (Box 214, Folder 9)
- Local 317, 1959-1961 (Box 214, Folder 10)
- Local 294, 1959-1962 (Box 214, Folder 11)
- Local 317, 1964-1967 (Box 214, Folder 12)
- Teamsters, 1960-1963 (Box 215, Folder 1)
- Teamsters, Ind. Master Contract (Bottling Cos.), 1959-1964 (Box 215, Folder 2)
- Local 182 A-B, 1964-1968 (Box 215, Folder 3)
- Local 182 C-F, 1965-1968 (Box 215, Folder 4)
- Local 182 G-L, 1964-1967 (Box 215, Folder 5)
- Local 182 M-T, 1964-1967 (Box 215, Folder 6)
- Local 182 U-Z, 1964-1967 (Box 215, Folder 7)
- Local 202 A-O, 1965-1968 (Box 215, Folder 8)
- Local 202 P-Z, 1964 (Box 215, Folder 9)
- Local 232, 1964-1968 (Box 215, Folder 10)
- Local 237, 1964-1967 (Box 215, Folder 11)
- Local 239, 1965-1968 (Box 215, Folder 12)
- Local 263, 1963-1966 (Box 215, Folder 13)
- Local 264, 1967 (Box 215, Folder 14)
- Local 272, 1968 (Box 215, Folder 15)
- Local 277, 1965-1968 (Box 215, Folder 16)
- Local 282 H-Z, 1968 (Box 215, Folder 17)
- Local 282 A-G, 1963-1968 (Box 215, Folder 18)
- Local 294 A, 1964-1967 (Box 215, Folder 19)
- Local 167, 1965-1967 (Box 216, Folder 1)
- Local 138, 1966-1968 (Box 216, Folder 2)
- Local 118 T-Z, 1964-1967 (Box 216, Folder 3)
- Local 135, 1978-1981 (Box 216, Folder 4)
- Local 118 R-S, 1964-1968 (Box 216, Folder 5)
- Local 118 L-N, 1964-1967 (Box 216, Folder 6)
- Local 118 O-Q, 1955 (Box 216, Folder 7)
- Local 118 D-K, 1964-1967 (Box 216, Folder 8)
- Local 118 A-C, 1956-1964 (Box 216, Folder 9)
- Local 99, 1965-1968 (Box 216, Folder 10)
- Local 80, 1965-1967 (Box 216, Folder 11)
- Local 65, 1963-1965 (Box 216, Folder 12)
- Local 62, 1965-1968 (Box 216, Folder 13)
- Local 46, 1967-1968 (Box 216, Folder 14)
- Local 39, 1964-1966 (Box 216, Folder 15)
- Local 27, 1964-1967 (Box 216, Folder 16)
- Master Freight Agreement (1975-) (Box 216, Folder 17)
- Local 933, 1970-1978 (Box 217, Folder 1)
- Local 918 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 217, Folder 2)